这位少爷
我求求你你放过我吧
我根本就不是张文杰的亲妈
我也不是什么哑巴
那个沈魏英才是他亲妈
你们快去找他吧
啊你说什么
笑个寨还能遇到这种奇葩事
沈桂英是谁
赶紧说
沈桂英是俺娘买给俺哥的媳妇
他才是张梦洁的亲妈
我就是一时糊涂想霸占张家的财产
才把他金锁抢走了
顶替了他的身份
还还什么
快住还
还想找机会让他消失
哼你这老不死的该不是在骗我
我可是听说了骗会上亲子鉴定的
证明了你就是他亲妈
这个报告是我交换过的
我根本就根本一点关系都没有
你该不会是在胡老子
沈冰那个老罪鬼可是亲口承认
你就是他亲姐
哎呀他也是我派人花钱找来的
我根本就不认识他
李秀芳才是我亲娘
我从小就生长在小枣村
我怎么敢骗你呀啊
原来富常说的都是真的
沈桂英才是你的亲生母亲
无论你在哪里
妈妈都会找到你和你团聚
沈桂英才是我的亲妈
是我一直错怪了
这下这下我可以走了吧
你看到了吗
这就是你找了20年的亲妈
This young master
I beg you, please let me go
I'm not Zhang Wenjie's mother at all
I'm not dumb either
That Shen Weiying is his biological mother
Go find him
Ah what did you say
Laughing at the village can still encounter such a strange thing
Who is Shen Guiying?
Say it now
Shen Guiying is the daughter-in-law my mother bought for my brother
He is Zhang Mengjie's mother
I was just confused and wanted to seize the property of the Zhang family
Just stole his golden lock
Replaced his identity
What else?
Stay here
I still want to find a chance to make him disappear
Hmph, you immortal are not lying to me
I heard about the paternity test
Proves that you are his mother
I exchanged this report
I had nothing to do with it.
Are you in Hu Laozi?
Shen Bing, the old criminal, admitted it himself
You are his sister
Oh, I sent someone to pay for him too.
I don't even know him.
Li Xiufang is my mother
I grew up in Xiaozao Village
How dare I lie to you!
It turns out that what Fu Chang said is true
Shen Guiying is your biological mother
Wherever you are
Mom will find you and reunite with you
Shen Guiying is my biological mother
I've been wrong
Now I can go now
Did you see it?
This is the mother you've been looking for for 20 years